

# Alipasha Askerov

Mail: askerovpasha21@gmail.com

Phone: +994 (055) 322 0718

Address: 37 Bakikhanov Street, Baku, Azerbaijan

· Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/alipasha-askerov-868213246/

Portfolio: alipashaskerov.netlify.app/

· Github: github.com/pashaskerov21

## **Summary**

I have been developing myself in the field of Frontend Developer for 3 years now and I have experience with many technologies, I am improving myself in this field. Currently, I am working in the field of Frontend Development. I am experienced in developing powerful websites that meet client goals. Able to identify needs, create plans, and work with clients to optimize design usability and performance. I can work effectively without supervision and learn new skills quickly. I develop web pages that are responsive to all devices in a form according to the wishes of the clients. I have a great passion for programming and am constantly improving my knowledge in this field.

### **Hard Skills**

HTML

React JS

¡Query

React Router

SQL

Gitbash

· Figma

 CSS SCSS  Next JS TypeScript

 Redux Axios

 RESTFUL API
JSON PHP

• GIT

 Bootstrap Tailwind CSS  Adobe XD · Responsive Design

JavaScript
Angular JS

React Hooks
Laravel

Github

• Styled Components • Microsoft Office

#### Soft Skills

Problem solving

 Customer service Adaptability

 Accountability Patience

 Communication Teamwork

Self-learning

Collaboration

Creativity

• Time management • Attention to detail

## **Work Experience**

Front End Developer

12/2022 - Current

**Proton MMC** 

Address: Ahmad Rajabli 156, Narimanov, Baku

Front End Developer Intern

10/2022 - 12/2022

**Proton MMC** 

Address: Ahmad Rajabli 156, Narimanov, Baku

Automation Engineer Intern

02/2022 - 06/2022

Azersu OJSC

Address: Baku, Azerbaijan

#### Education

Azerbaijan State Oil and Industry University

09/2018 - 07/2022

**Bachelor of Science:** Process Automation Engineering

Address: 28 May, Baku, Azerbaijan

Azerbaijan State Oil and Industry University

09/2022 - 07/2024

Master of Science: Automation of Technological Processes and Production

Address: 28 May, Baku, Azerbaijan

# Language

- Engilsh B1 (Intermediate)
- · Azerbaijani native language